// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The church that was commended for giving even when in extreme poverty was in?",
    answer: "Macedonia",
    options: [
      "Corinth",
      "Galatia",
      "Thessalonica",
      "Macedonia"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "When did the Israelites say All that the Lord has spoken we will do?",
    answer: "At mount Sinai",
    options: [
      "At mount Sinai",
      "Before crossing the red sea",
      "After the golden calf incident",
      "At mount Horeb"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Saul was rejected as king over Israel because he disobeyed God's command to utterly destroy the?",
    answer: "Amalekites",
    options: [
      "Assyrian",
      "Philistines",
      "Amalekites",
      "Ammonites"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Naaman's Leprosy was transferred to Gehazi because Gehazi was?",
    answer: "covetous",
    options: [
      "Ambitious",
      "covetous",
      "Contemptuous",
      "Anxious"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In Thessalonians, Paul advises believers awaiting the coming of the Lord to put on the?",
    answer: "Breast plate of faith",
    options: [
      "Armour of hope",
      "Breast plate of faith",
      "Helmet of righteousness",
      "Breast plate of salvation"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "In order that Benjamin might be brought to Egypt Joseph detained",
  answer: "Simeon",
  options: [
    "Simeon",
    "Reuben",
    "Judah",
    "Levi"
  ]
},
{
numb: 7,
question: "My father Chastised you with whips, but I will chastise you with scorpion. Who said this?",
answer: "Jeroboam",
options: [
  "Rehoboam",
  "Jeroboam",
  "Absalom",
  "Solomon"
]
},
{
numb: 8,
question: "The disciples were for the first time called Christians in?",
answer: "Antioch",
options: [
  "Jerusalem",
  "Antioch",
  "Tarsus",
  "Judea"
]
},
{
numb: 9,
question: "Abraham is portrayed in the Bible as?",
answer: " The father of the Faithful",
options: [
  " The father of the Faithful",
  "The law giver",
  "Man of covenant",
  "Father of the world"
]
},
{
numb: 10,
question: "Rahab the harlot assisted the Israelites spies as they prepare to attack",
answer: "Jericho",
options: [
  "Amonites",
  "Jericho",
  "Gibeon",
  "Ai"
]
},
{
numb: 11,
question: "When prophet Isaiah saw the Lord of hosts in the Temple he?",
answer: "condemned himself and his people",
options: [
  "was ashamed of himself",
  "praised his glory",
  "condemned himself and his people",
  "prayed fervently"
]
}
];